<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ETAIS</title>
    <link>https://f4ww4z.github.io/etais-web/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on ETAIS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://f4ww4z.github.io/etais-web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-service guide is out</title>
      <link>https://f4ww4z.github.io/etais-web/2017/05/31/self-service-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f4ww4z.github.io/etais-web/2017/05/31/self-service-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are rolling out a self-service for accessing and managing ETAIS resources
in a user friendly non-bureaucratic manner. The first version of user guide is
&lt;a href=&#34;https://etais-ee.github.io/etais-web/self_service/&#34;&gt;available now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETAIS is hiring new people</title>
      <link>https://f4ww4z.github.io/etais-web/2017/04/12/career-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f4ww4z.github.io/etais-web/2017/04/12/career-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On April 7 ETAIS project managers took part in Institute of Computer Science career day to find new talents for ETAIS project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The event was a success as three people were invited to an interview and a test job in Tartu University&amp;rsquo;s HPC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year three people were already hired: Ilja Livenson (cloud solutions, self-service portal and much more),
Tõnu Raitviir (cyber safety in all its forms) and Rutt Lindström (information safety in processes and documentation).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ETAIS is a growing project. You too are welcome to contact us if you can and truly wish to contribute to the project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETAIS-2 has kicked off</title>
      <link>https://f4ww4z.github.io/etais-web/2017/03/05/etais2-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f4ww4z.github.io/etais-web/2017/03/05/etais2-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The four parties of ETAIS consortium have started a new project to make ETAIS great again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;University of Tartu, Tallinn University of Technology, National Institute of Chemical Physics and Biophysics and Information Technology Foundation for Education have started a new ETAIS project that aims to integrate the infrastructures created during the previous ETAIS project and improve data storage. A brand new component of ETAIS project will be a self-service portal that allows users to access the resources regardless of their location or operating system used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ETAIS infrastructure will continue to be divided between the institutions – the project’s main goal is to optimise resources and share costs (mainly staff and electricity) between partners. It is also important that the project’s partners create a shared knowledge base and therefore improve the quality of the ETAIS services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project consists of the following sub-projects:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting up cloud service&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting up a self-service portal&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Renewal of the authentication system TAAT (TAAT2)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increasing computing and data storing capability (additional hardware)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing information security system ISKE&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Starting a new and more lively website for ETAIS project :)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The project is funded by European Regional Development Fund.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New web page</title>
      <link>https://f4ww4z.github.io/etais-web/2017/03/01/new-webpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f4ww4z.github.io/etais-web/2017/03/01/new-webpage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As you can see, ETAIS project has moved to a brand new website powered by Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The new website is to replace an old WordPress one that needed to retire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for the new one - we are right now filling it up with information about ETAIS project and its members and contributors.
We aim to add a blog and many useful user guides.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would be happy to get your feedback about this page. Whenever you feel like something
important is missing or could be better or different, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to let us know or do it yourself
through a pull request: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/etais-ee/etais-web&#34;&gt;https://github.com/etais-ee/etais-web&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>